adultmatchdoctor.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement for Matchdoctor.com**  
(Last Revised: February 7, 2006) 

Online Singles, LLC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to our users' privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Matchdoctor.com. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our website, and for locally targeted ads. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. 

Cookies and AdSense 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your preferences. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes, such as using and placing cookies to help display optimized advertisements. 

Third parties, such as Google AdSense, our main advertising network, may place and read cookies on your browser, or use web beacons to collect information, while serving ads on this site. Here is how Google explains what a cookie is: 

"A 'cookie' is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies." 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information such as email address and date of birth; also, optional information such as demographic information like their zip code, age, or income level. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user communications from our web site. We do not share customer contact information with third parties, unless the user authorizes us to. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data are also collected at our site. We use this data for other purposes including: tailoring the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. We may also use the date to display relevant ads to the user. You always have the right to opt-out. Please contact us if you have any problems at all opting-out or if you fear your email address was abused. Note that your private information may be given out in response to any police-type investigation, subpoena, or other request pending a lawsuit, legal action or billing inquiry. 

Your profile on Matchdoctor.com will not contain your name, email address, IP address, real world address (but will display city), or password. It may reveal other information about you that you chose to display. Be sure to view your own profile to make sure you are only displaying the information you desire to be displayed. 

This site is a dating community and networking site. The intent of the site is for people to meet and communicate with other people, and thus all profiles and all content (including all user created content) on this site are considered in the public domain. They are viewable by people who are not members of ours site in many ways, including but not limited to Who's Online, New Photos, New Users, New Blogs, refer a friend, permalinks, and our menu links. In addition, as we are a free to use site, anyone can sign up and immediately view all non-hidden/cancelled profiles, all user created content, and any other public portion of this site. Search engines may crawl and index our content as well. Private content/information such as your email address, sent and received mail, etc. is **not** in the public domain, is only viewable by you, this site's staff, and is **not** crawlable by search engines. 

**Public Forums**  
This site may make chat rooms, forums, blogs, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Search engines may also crawl and index our forums. 

**Links**  
Matchdoctor.com contains links to sites. Matchdoctor.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Matchdoctor.com. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for canceling their profile and to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  * You can change your mail preferences by signing into your settings.
  * To stop all emails and cancel your account as well, click here.

**Correct/Update**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  * Visit your profile details page by clicking here.
  * LAST OPTION: Submit a support ticket.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us.
